


let questions = [{
  numb: 1,
  question: "How many players play a football martch?",
  answer: "11", options: [
    "11", 
    "10", 
    "9",
    "12"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 2,
  question: "How many tooth does a human have?",
  answer: "32",
  options: [
    "20",
    "42",
    "32",
    "None of the above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 3,
  question: "What are the types of gender?",
  answer: "female, male",
  options: [
    "female, male",
    "male, female, trans",
    "Both",
    "None of the above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 4,
  question: "What age in Ghana shows you are an adult?",
  answer: "18+",
  options: [
    "30+",
    "40+",
    "16+",
    "18+"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 5,
  question: "What language is spoken in Ghana",
  answer: "Twi",
  options: [
    "Twi",
    "Latin",
    "French",
    "All the above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: "What are are the colours of the Ghana flag?",
  answer: "Red, green, yellow, black",
  options: [
    "Green white black",
    "Red, yellow, black, green, brown",
    "Red, yellow, green, brown",
    "Red, green, yellow, black"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "How many region do Ghana have?",
  answer: "16",
  options: [
    "10",
    "12",
    "14",
    "16"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "How many local districts does Ghana have?",
  answer: "216",
  options: [
    "200",
    "210",
    "216",
    "220"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "when did Ghana establish the former ten regions?",
  answer: "1987",
  options: [
    "1957",
    "1987",
    "1960",
    "1844"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "How was Ghana called back in the days?",
  answer: "Gold caost",
  options: [
    "Ghana empire",
    "Ghana",
    "Gold caost",
    "None of the above"
  ]
}
];
